<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LiteWeight</string>
    <string name="no_workouts_found">
        No workouts found. Create one to get lifting!
    </string>
    <string name="nav_draw_open">Open Nav</string>
    <string name="nav_draw_close">Close Nav</string>
    <string name="nav_title">Weigh Your Options</string>
    <string name="new_workout_title">Create Workout</string>
    <string name="number_of_weeks">Number of Weeks</string>
    <string name="number_of_days">Number of Days</string>
    <string name="workout_name_title">Workout Name</string>
    <string name="video_url_hint">Video URL</string>
    <string name="week_input_hint">Period of workout (1&#8211;10)</string>
    <string name="fixed_workout_day_input_hint">Days in each week (1&#8211;7)</string>
    <string name="flexible_workout_day_input_hint">Total days in workout</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="default_workout_marker">Week/Day</string>
    <string name="ignore_weight">Ignore Weight</string>
    <string name="empty_workout_day">No exercises for this day. Click the plus button below to add some.</string>
    <string name="unsaved_workout_msg">You have a workout currently being created. If you quit now, all progress
    will be lost!\n\nAre you sure you wish to quit?</string>
    <string name="popup_message_edit_workout">You have a workout currently being edited. If you quit now, all progress
    will be lost!\n\nAre you sure you wish to quit?</string>
    <string name="popup_message_create_workout_help">There are currently two types of workouts you can create: "fixed" and "flexible".
        \n\nFixed workouts have a fixed number of weeks and days. So for example if you put 4 for the weeks and 4 for the days, there will be 16 days total.
        \n\nFlexible workouts allow you to create a workout that only has sequential days. So if you input 20, there will be 20 days in the workout.
        \n\nNote that while you can edit the specific exercises and name of a workout after you create it, you cannot alter the number of days in it regardless of the workout type.</string>
    <string name="video_switch_description">Provides a play button next to each exercise in the current workout page that, when
    clicked, launches a video using the provided URL for the specific exercise.</string>
    <string name="metric_switch_description">Converts all units in the app from imperial units (lb) to metric units (kg).</string>
    <string name="stopwatch_switch_description">Provides a simple stopwatch at the bottom of the current workout page. If the app is put in the background the stopwatch will continue to run.</string>
    <string name="timer_switch_description">Provides a simple timer at the bottom of the current workout page. To change the timer duration, click the timer when it is not running.
        If the app is put in the background the timer will continue to run.</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="select_focus_title">Select Focus(s)</string>
    <string name="new_exercise_title">New Exercise</string>
    <string name="url_hint">Video URL (Leave empty for none)</string>
    <string name="name_hint">Exercise Name</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="weight">Weight</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="video_switch">Videos</string>
    <string name="stopwatch_switch">Stopwatch</string>
    <string name="timer_switch">Timer</string>
    <string name="focus_label">Focus</string>
    <string name="save_url">Save URL</string>
    <string name="new_url">New Video URL</string>
    <string name="preview_url">View (Old)</string>
    <string name="copy_url">Copy (Old)</string>
    <string name="edit_weight">Edit weight</string>
    <string name="save_weight">Save weight</string>
    <string name="version_number">Version </string>
    <string name="exercise_not_found">Exercise not found.</string>
    <string name="search_exercise_hint">Enter exercise name.</string>
    <string name="filter_default">Filter Default</string>
    <string name="my_exercises">My Exercises</string>
    <string name="exercise_label">Exercise</string>
    <string name="nav_divider_title">Locker Room</string>
    <string name="workout_list_title">Workout List</string>
    <string name="nav_workout_icon_title">Current Workout</string>
    <string name="nav_list_icon_title">My Workouts</string>
    <string name="rename_title">Rename</string>
    <string name="edit_workout_tooltip">Edit Workout Name</string>
    <string name="nav_user_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="nav_about">About</string>
    <string name="forward_button">Next</string>
    <string name="metric_switch">Metric</string>
    <string name="workout_progress">Workout Progress</string>
    <string name="workout_type_switch">Fixed Workout</string>
    <string name="delete_workout_title">Delete Workout?</string>
    <string name="reset_statistics">Reset Statistics</string>
    <string name="restart_msg">Do you wish to restart this workout?\n\nIf so, you will be taken back
    to the first day of the workout with all exercises unchecked.
        \n\nThe statistics for this workout will be updated using the current workout progress.</string>
    <string name="delete_msg">Are you sure you wish to permanently delete this workout?\n\nIf so, all statistics for it will also be deleted.</string>
    <string name="delete_custom_exercise_msg">
        Are you sure you wish to delete this exercise? All data regarding this exercise will be deleted.
        \n\nNote that deleting it will remove it from already made workouts.
    </string>
    <string name="exercise_title">Add exercises</string>
    <string name="start_button">Start</string>
    <string name="stop_button">Stop</string>
    <string name="hide_stopwatch">Hide</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="show_stopwatch">Stopwatch</string>
    <string name="show_timer">Timer</string>
    <string name="timer_title"><u>Timer</u></string>
    <string name="stopwatch_title"><u>Stopwatch</u></string>
    <string name="minutes_title">Minutes</string>
    <string name="seconds_title">Seconds</string>
    <string name="time_picker_title">Pick Time</string>
    <string name="save_time">Save Time</string>
    <string name="add_exercises">Add Exercises</string>
    <string name="about_overview_title">App Overview</string>
    <string name="username_and_email_hint"><i>Username/Email</i></string>
    <string name="username_hint"><i>Username</i></string>
    <string name="password_hint"><i>Password</i></string>
    <string name="password_confirm_hint"><i>Confirm Password</i></string>
    <string name="email_hint"><i>Email</i></string>
    <string name="display_name_hint"><i>Display Name</i></string>
    <string name="sign_in">SIGN IN</string>
    <string name="sign_up">SIGN UP</string>
    <string name="guest_btn">CONTINUE AS GUEST</string>
    <string name="about_overview">
        LiteWeight is an open source lightweight workout manager that allows for multiple workouts to be created and managed. Workouts can be fixed in size either by weeks or sequential days, and can be cycled indefinitely with relevant statistics tracked.
        \n\nDefault exercises are provided by the developer, and, if desired, you can add your own custom exercises to be used in any workout!
        All exercises can have a URL associated with them should you wish to be able to view a video on how to perform one while working out.
        You can also set the most recent amount of weight for specific exercises and this weight will carry over to all your workouts.\n\nAll data is saved locally on your phone in a database, and in the future functionality for cloud storage may become available.
    </string>
    <string name="about_nav_overview_title">Navigation Overview</string>
    <string name="about_nav_overview"><u><b>Current Workout:</b></u> Your currently selected workout. You can mark an exercise as done, update the weight of an exercise, or watch the video associated with it if you have that option enabled.
        When done you can restart the workout and all exercises will be unchecked and you will be brought back to the beginning of the workout. Alternatively, hold down the \"Next\" button to activate a shortcut to restart the workout from any day.
        If enabled in the settings page, a timer or stopwatch is provided. These will run in the background as long as the app is not terminated.
        \n\n<u><b>My Workouts:</b></u> Where all of your workouts are located. The workout at the top is the currently selected one. To switch the current workout, you can select any of your workouts that appear in the list.
        To create new workouts, click the plus button at the bottom of the page. You can rename, edit, reset statistics, or delete the current workout by clicking the three dots next to the current workout.
        \n\n<u><b>My Exercises:</b></u> Exercises, both custom and default, are listed in this section, and the weights and URL associated with the exercises can be modified.
        \n\n<u><b>Settings:</b></u> This section allows for any user settings to be enabled or disabled. These changes will persist upon the closing of the app.
    </string>
    <string name="acknowledgements_title">Acknowledgements</string>
    <string name="acknowledgements">App graphic was created using a vector made by <a href="https://www.flaticon.com/free-icon/gym_755336?term=weight&amp;page=1&amp;position=3">Monkik</a>.
        \n\nMy Exercises Icon was created by <a href="https://thenounproject.com/demograph/uploads/?i=149086">Demograph</a>.
    </string>
</resources>
